And good evening. Welcome to another
episode of Exar Talk Show. Today uh
we're going to do randomish. So I'm just
going to do my usual working session.
This is ultimate hacking keyboard I have
review on my website. Okay. Ultimate
hacking keyboard and this is fantastic
trackboard. This is Nia
M572
or something. Nia China cheapo. That's
what I call them because they are cheap
and f and fantastic. Okay. You can get
on Amazon or check out search my
YouTube. I have reviews. Okay. Now let's
see switch to my screen so you can see
my screen and uh disappear this Google.
Um, so my Emac power. Okay.
So, what are we doing? So, randomish.
Okay. I don't have any particular goal.
So, you just going to see me get drunk.
It's the most the for most important
thing. And watch my Emacs masturbation.
You powerful.
Okay, let's have a drink.
rum, spice, rum, something. Okay, we're
going to have two shots today.
And today we going to use this advanced
high tech tall shot. This is like 1.5
shot.
Fantastic and beautiful. Can you see?
You see you are looking at my Firefox
browser and there are like something
like few hundred tabs.
All those are my website I'm working on.
So I can show you some. For example,
this is todo. You know, my todo, they
just pile up year after year. So,
there's JavaScript watts I'm compiling.
Uh, it's funny. I haven't ever compiled
it, but now I'm starting to, you know,
after 10 [snorts] 10 years of JavaScript
in depth.
Uh, JavaScript watts. You can look at it
if you want. Just search it. I think
you'll find it because it's been there
for at least a week a week. So I'm I'm
you see the purpose of this page is to
compile a list of the JavaScript watts.
You know JavaScript is one of the worst
programming language. Funny you see the
most like I I mentioned this before the
most popular programming languages C,
C++, PHP, JavaScript and Python. They
turns out they are the worst. Okay. So
uh so I would say among them C++ and
JavaScript are the worst.
Python you know it's not very good. C
not very good. Well C is pretty pretty
bad. It is it's pretty worst you know
like imagine to these days in C you
don't have a module system like name
space you know like the [ __ ] idiotic
C scumbags
to this day you don't have like the C
programming language
no name space no module system you
include you slurp the files into your
program like you know that pile of [ __ ]
but but But but the thing is C
programmers they are they form a cult
with Unix. So they just
we we are the fastest you know we are
bare metal you know the [ __ ] sea
fuckets
you know so so I despise them so much
anyway
uh let's not be too sad. Okay let's keep
drinking.
[laughter]
Okay. So my discord um
so we are in the age of AI maners.
Now remember a few years you know like
six years ago. So this is my Twitter
Twitter tweet tweet tweetless
Twitter created by deep state. You know
you can like if you do live stream you
realize you can see yourself the
history. You see this is six years ago.
I you know I was browsing my um S talk
show because I was trying to find you
know I found some bad named date you
know this file don't have a date you
know anyway so so right now they are
1,000 over 1,000
star talk show you know so today's
episode is what
today's episode is 800 something and you
know so I've done 800 videos since 2000
19. Okay, so I just run into this, you
know, [laughter]
uh god [ __ ] stupid Twitter. Uh, you
know, so this so this is 20 um 20. Okay,
so you can uh see history of yourself
when you do live stream. Uh it's that's
one of the side effect, you know. So
this this never happened before. This is
like technology, you know. you started
to you can you know before you do you
write diary you know I don't know if you
zoomers know what does diary mean you
know but you know you used to people
write you know right do you know what
he's writing you know maybe you guys
don't know but
hello hello hello G K4
K hello an
um you know writing
oh John Civor died yesterday. Oh [ __ ]
That's in, you know, that's interesting.
I kind of know the guy, John C. Vorak.
He he he's he he's a uh what they call
the tech um uh the the Gatfly, you know,
he he he he's a he writes about
technology about programming languages
since like 80s or even 70s before me. So
he keeps writing. Uh so I didn't so he
passed away. I didn't know. So I for a
period of time
uh I was following him somewhat. Um
uh Nick Bernstein he's working on
closure.
Um anyway so well let's uh let's let's
just uh random search. Okay let's see
John. Oh [ __ ] I don't want to search my
own.
uh after 30 years I have a understanding
of the C++ Unix type of coders. Okay,
that's a tweet I posted two days ago. Uh
it's about my hatred of the C C++
programmers because I realized
you know I I realized this uh I think
even 10 years ago that the CC++
programmers these type of people you can
classify they actually they have some
sort of personality mentality. Okay,
they are the doers and hackers but
however they are incapable of abstract
thinking or design or architecture or
philosophy like you ask them anything
about th you know in those area design
uh architecture
or abstract you know thinking or
philosophy they they don't know like you
know so this is a classification so
those people who tends to be just doers
not thinkers I'm a thinker. Okay, I'm
I'm I'm not a doer. I cannot do much.
Okay, so you know like you know there's
a coding competition. You know this, you
know, people can code fast and they just
code.
But so but but the so people have
different personalities, different areas
where you are good or you are not so
good. So those people those uh generally
speaking okay not apply does not apply
to everyone but those people who likes C
and C++ and Unix are kind of these dos
okay and they they are not good at
uh philosophy like they don't know much
they are not good at design like they
can't design [ __ ] you know the best
thing they came out is Unix [laughter]
command line crap you know confusing
complexity can design a [ __ ]
they can't think of architecture you
know in extensibility they can't you
know so so for example when there are a
lot of people in my um kind of
in my community like functional
programmers skim this for example
so they you know we we we you know we we
we see you know we our criticism on C
and stuff, but when you argue with the C
people, they don't see it. They they
don't understand what you're talking
about. Like completely don't understand
what you're talking about. It's a C C++
type of people,
you know, and they they they will just
laugh at you. No, look, we our our code
is the fastest. We are the the most
popular cockroaches, you know. We run
all the fundamental structures,
[laughter]
which is like lying to themselves. They
don't know but they that's how what they
you know that's what they are like this
type of people. So this is about like
personality classification
and one of the most popular famous guy
I believe that represent that class of
people is John Carmarmac. You know John
Carmarmac the famous for his uh game
programming ID software. You know this
guy [laughter]
this guy I cannot tolerate. You know you
listen to his talk interview by that
that that deep state guy. you know the
anyway he he's got videos right you
listen to you don't know what he's
talking about like
you know John J John John John Carmarmac
but of course a lot programmers admire
like him you know like John Carmarmac is
a hero he's a genius and who are these
people who admire John Karmac you you
look at them you realize they are not
mathematicians they are not great
functional programmer as you know,
creator of Lisp, creator of Hascal,
creator of Okamo, creator of, you know,
the the the the inventor of the uh type
theory. No, that's not the those people
who uh admire John Carmarmac are the C
and C++ coders
inevitably
always. [laughter]
[ __ ] funny. [ __ ] funny. [ __ ]
the [ __ ] these people. So anyway to be
sure you know so we are just like
different uh you know type of people
that's all okay that's what I'm saying
that's what I'm saying
uh so uh so okay so that's uh that's my
thought about you know anyway I was
going to uh we we were going to search
for like the uh Vorac guy today's news
let's see what trader is you know
usually when you read Twitter
either you don't read it if you try to
read the news it's like ugly the you
know the politicians or the death and
killings AI video dream of futuristic
Tesla robbo taxi with beds and empty
caps AI video what the [ __ ] Turk Carson
okay Turk Carson you know
uh I think he's a great guy but that's
politics ics. So, we better not talk
about it. Candace Owen. Okay, that's
another politics. Let's better not talk
about it. Okay, let's uh pretend
nothing, you know, nothing is going
going to nothing is happening. Uh so
there we have it. John C. Vorac
you know the funny that you know so this
guy is you know writing about tech you
know and Adam Curry Adam Curry
so he John Civorak and Adam Curry since
like 10 years ago they started a podcast
called which I was listening for a while
uh anyway I I don't want to go through
this Twitter you know like when when you
go through Twitter you know
it just become ugly ugly and drama and
all the corruption you know like you
know so anyway so
I hope I'm making sense but Adam Curry
he's also very old I think 70 something
but he's a guy who kind of created
podcast the idea like one of the first
or something he created podcast idea
okay I don't know him too much uh and he
and John Corak they created a podcast
called Um
I listened I listened like five years
ago you know when when I was the on
master someone introduced me I think
George introduced me to master then you
know on discord. So uh my discord
friends.
So sometimes I just random you know uh
talk about programming languages like
here I was talking about why was why was
I installing uh Rust yesterday.
So anyway so yeah so they they they have
a podcast like political you know
talking about politics. So John Civak
died so anything what else? Um,
cheers.
But I do remember like a few articles by
John C. Vorac like back in like I I I
remember there's some article he wrote
back in 1980s that was before I was
involved in computer like he was like
when Unix was coming up you know he was
criticizing Unix or something and then
[snorts] in 1990s when Mac you know was
popular like Mac versus PC you know you
guys are young you guys don't know but
but Mac versus PC is a thing you know
Like even today, not so much today, but
back in the 1990s, like everyone like
perpetually talk about Mac versus PC,
you know, like the PC people, we we'll
just ridicule Mac, you know, saying that
it's for kids.
Mac versus PC. Can Can I find some
other, you know, I have a funny picture.
Let me show you that. So that's Emacs.
No, I don't want Emacs. minus EMAC
uh list Marco versus Wuam language.
Okay, I have like uh 13,000 articles.
Okay, speed compar comparison Mac Mini
2014 versus PC 2019. Anyway, so um let's
see.
Switch to
Windows. Okay, so that's one of my
article why I am switching from Mac to
Windows written in 2009.
So, Mag um so there's a picture there's
a funny picture I just want to show you
that okay by the way this this article
is for you guys who constantly ask me
why are you why are you on Windows why
are you on Windows like ask me that
every every every month
but anyway so there's a funny um picture
I want to show you okay so where is it
Um,
where is it? Where the [ __ ] is it?
Cheers.
Cheers. And cheers. And cheers. Rum.
Uh, here you are looking at a picture of
my power station when I was dying of
hunger.
2009.
You don't you you wouldn't understand.
Okay. Like I explain what do you mean
dying of hunger? You guys wouldn't
understand. But um there it is a picture
of me. I mean the my desk my power
station. Okay. Today I'm doing much
better. Thank you guys. Uh so there is a
funny well this is one of them. Okay.
Like funny picture. That's what people
think, you know. Some people like make
fun of Mac. Mac is beautiful for $4,000,
you know, but PC is look looking like
that $1,000, but you can do, you know,
play 3D games like that, you know. So,
people make fun of uh Mac. But you see
the thing about Mac, it's truly
beautiful designed. Yeah. Well, they
it's expensive. They, you know, they try
to make money. But the design the
software the even if you are a
programmer not just for looks not just
for like you know people who don't know
nothing you know just look know
beautiful but if you are a programmer
you know like even back then you know
hyper hyper card and lots of things Mac
draw you know that revolutionized
the computing industry not just the
physical computer looks you know for
example you got for example I got the
iMac here one piece very elegant, right?
Well, tends to be slow and more
expensive. That's true because Apple you
know Apple they they they try to make
money and also you got this beautiful
you know iMac which is a thing but the
thing but the thing about Mac it's not
just the physical like pretty but the
the design the software the user
interface and the programming language
the architecture of the Mac the you know
how you um how shall you say you know
you got Apple script you got you know
lots of things and also So back then
lisp was one of the primary thing
running on Mac and and lots of
innovation
in software in software too apple talk
and lots of things. Okay. So the the
there is a design there's a brand going
into it
opposite of the Unix [ __ ] and Unix
and C [ __ ] you know they just they
just we we are the fast you know the
crap complexity crap okay that's my
thought about Apple okay all these years
so Apple revolutionized you know like
you guys you know how to convey the idea
but Apple revolutioniz ized the idea of
for example graphical user interface.
You know, today we obviously you use a
mouse. Obviously, you know, [laughter]
obviously, but that's not the case in
the in the 1990s on the on the Windows,
you know. So, let me show you the
picture. Okay. So, um so I got that that
funny picture I want to show you.
Am I doing well? So, you guys comment.
Okay. Concurrent viewers, how many?
Let's see. Uh, is it one three? Okay,
three is the crowd.
So, let me show you the Yeah, I want to
show you that funny picture. Where is
it? [sighs]
Cheers.
So yesterday I installed Rust. So you
know we'll see my journey with Rust. Um
I don't know where it went but but I can
find it. So stop the video here. Okay.
What are you seeing? Uh so go to
kasadi.org
uh or kasadi.org showing browser. So I
have two websites kasadi.org
that was since two year 2000 I
registered the domain kasadi.org
and since about 2010 I started to have
kasadi.info.
I started to separate the content. So
kasali.info
open that
hacker code open that kasali.info is
it's all about programming and
mathematics basically technical stuff
and unic code. Okay. And keyboard. So,
so you got the unic code all all kind of
things and keyboard technology review
and uh random chat opinions and uh
character frequency plot you can type.
So select go type it will show the
frequency as you type that's JavaScript
TypeScript technology okay
uh I wrote it of course uh so you got
keyboards then you got okay this this is
kind of fun Chinese chess you know let
me show you guys how to play Chinese
chess okay is similar to the western
chess
but it's more like you got more freedom
like in western chess you got the issue
of congestion
like you can't move nothing like because
you got the pawns and pawns forms a
structure very
which is actually very good you know
very um dense game the pawn you know
where where you move your pawn is is
critical not so much in Chinese chess
Chinese chess is more freedom like you
can like you can immediately attack.
Okay. So they, you know, that's a rook.
Okay. So, you know, so that's a r rook.
It's coming out. So, let's let me just
do that. Chinese chess. Okay. Very fun.
I'm pretty good. You know, I I was um
So anyway, so I was saying, so I was
saying
sorry.info.
So I was saying you know so I moved all
the computing and technical stuff to
kasali.info
while the kasali.org or contains things
like
English stuff, vocabulary, literature,
writing style, logic of linguist,
linguistics and uh you know those kind
of things hundreds of articles and
there's a artificial artificial language
today is called constructed language
logebang okay I was learning it 20 years
ago
some somewhat. Okay. So I mean so so
kasali.org
is my you know original domain. So you
got English stuff writing and
literature'ses for example you got
classic literature'ses Arabian nightites
by sir Richard Francis Burton I talked
about often all these are my favorite
literature'ses flatland Romans of many
dimensions and the time machine I talked
about it a few times a tragedy the
tragedy of Titus Andronicus this is
Shakespeare okay like you you you well
you guys don't know okay This this is
Shakespeare know this one of the
greatest okay Shakespeare the tragedy of
Titus Andronicus
uh I came to love love Shakespeare like
[clears throat] you know 30 years ago
when I was younger I was I don't know
you know much you know like most of you
I mean when you are younger you don't
know much uh then
I I heard people talk about Shakespeare
and I was thinking what the [ __ ] is it
you know like so many people talk talk
about Shakespeare this or that but I I
came to really truly love Shakespeare
you know I just love Shakespeare's
writing
I love it okay Shakespeare and this tra
the tragedy of Titus Andronicus is my
favorite actually I haven't read much
about Shakespeare I think I read maybe
two or three plays total okay but but
this one I annotated so you can see
Actually
I learned it the hard way. So for every
word I don't understand I look up
dictionary. So I actually annotated so
you can see all these are my
annotations. You see assited asseted or
what what how you pronounce it goth
you know. So you learn a lot about
history too. History and English and you
know um Titus Andronicus. Okay.
And Alice in Wonderland. So you got
literature, you got uh ethmology.
Fascinating. You know, ethmology is a
pit of history. You you have a glimpse
of human history of past, let's say,
2,000 years of English ethmology.
There's also Chinese ones. That's that
that that's another story. Okay. But you
got, you know, ethmology.
Then you got dictionary geeking. I was,
you know, obsessed with looking up
dictionary. Anyway, so I told some of
these stories. Um, then there's Chinese,
um, my Chinese blog, which is not
frequently updated. Okay, Chinese is
like entire story by itself.
Linguistics, you know, Chinese Chinese
is even older. You know, Chinese is got
like basically 4,000 years of history.
Chinese
you know, Chinese Chinese. Yeah. 4,000.
So, so, so you can read some of, you
know, let me show you some of the um uh
Chinese uh Asian Chinese characters like
4,000 years ago. And you can still read
it.
Half of it is still legible to modern um
Chinese
people because the the characters remain
almost the same for 4,000 years. Okay.
uh you know so this is the like uh this
dictionary well known kangi dictionary
is like few hundred years old um anyway
so that's my some of my Chinese blog so
I wanted to show you yeah here so for
example you are looking at this this is
called oracle bone the the earliest re
uh record of Chinese character so this
is from oracle bone known from 600600
BC.
So that's
about 4,3,500
years ago. Okay.
Uh so this is like the kind of the
earliest Chinese character. Then it
evolved into that and evolved into you
know amazing this thing uh heavy you
know this cauldron and you can and you
know so for example this thing for
example this like bathtub thing is from
816 BC
about 3,000 years ago. Okay this thing
and you can read the characters these
are the characters. Okay. So to a modern
Chinese um you don't understand most of
the characters without training. But
some of them
uh you you can kind of guess. Okay. So
this is a beast. This is a rain or cloud
or you know something. This is person
probably this this this means heaven.
this character heaven this means no or
negative negation uh you know so anyway
Chinese characters okay se script and so
on and starting with seos script which
is 2000 I mean 200 uh 700 BC
all these we recognize almost every
character okay so they remain unchanged
for like two or 3,000
years Chinese.
So, you know, fascinating. So, all these
are uh part of my wordy English blog.
Then they are part it's part of
kasali.in uh kasali.org. So, you got
English and linguistics. Then you got
songs of human animals. Okay. So I have
about
500 songs
of human animals us that I annotated.
Okay, I'm digressing over. So So anyway,
so then I have some arts collection uh I
annotated. For example, you can look at
the white man's artwork. You know, this
is like famous white men's artwork.
Okay, I'm I'm kind of going boring, you
know. I'm just talking about my website,
which which I did talk about before.
Okay, so anyway, cha.org
is my original. Then there's my second
life exploration. This is around year
2009.
from 2007 to 2012. Okay. I explored I
basically lived in Second Life almost
six hours a day.
Tremendously fascinating. Okay. Second
Life,
you know, it's it's kind of my escapism.
Okay. So,
escapism,
you know, today you might see me drink
uh you know, got drunk. Some of you, you
know, like regulars here, George and
Francis, you know, you see me drunk and
you think,
uh, AI got into, you know, so AI kind of
made me sad because AI robbed my purpose
before AI, you know, two years ago, you
know, I'm a intellectual, you know, what
the white man would say, intellectual,
because I and I'm into programming stuff
and mathematics, so I You know I write
about Emacs. So that's
useful to some people, you know, at
least some people, a lot of people I
create Emacs packages or my opinions
about programming languages, right?
But with AI today, it robbed my
it robbed my, you know, that my my um
what what do you say the livelihood
because AI can answer everything
intellectually, you know, physics,
mathematics, whatever programming
language design, you can ask AI, it'll
answer. Of course, it grabbed all my
work. My my work is on AI database. I
showed that many times. If you search on
saudi.info search for AI, you'll find it
article where Google
you know Google AI database they have a
record you know they show my website on
their
list
right and you can see um
uh so you can see you know so AI you
know this is chat GPT talking about me
in 2023.
So Chad GBT knows everything about me,
you know, because it grabbed my entire
website,
Chad GBT, and wrote a poem about me in
2022.
Um, yeah. So, so today you you see me
like maybe I'm,
you know, I I feel sad. You know, AI has
gotten
uh me depressed, but but actually
that happened before. It's it's kind of
my chronic uh life experience uh kind of
depression kind of this uh
thing. Okay. Because for four years I I
lived in Second Life. Why part you know
really it's part of it you know it's
exploration of technology because Second
Life back then was like this something
incredible. Okay. It truly is. I had so
I had so much fun in Second Life. But on
the other hand, I was in it
uh you could say partly because I'm
somewhat it's a escapism. Okay, because
I don't want to deal with real life
stuff, you know. So I spent four years
in Second Life, okay? Anyway, that
that's a fantastic journey. I had so so
much fun in Second Life and I met a lot
of people.
Uh anyway, okay. So second life so then
so this is my kasari.org for you know
this is my original domain since year
2000. I started to write website in
1996.
So originally my website was hosted by
this uh by this university um
Swathmore
College uh something you know it changed
a few times but anyway originally
originally my website which is mostly
mathematics okay so my originally my
website let me show you okay
uh axali.info info. Originally my first
content, massive content is this
mathematics visual dictionary of special
plank codes and they were hosted on
universities like in USA Swathmore
College. Uh was it um
cheers
then for a few years I got hosted by
Phoenix
College kind of online you know there's
history so um
you know if you really want to know you
can search for it Uh I I have you know I
have blogged about them. SW A
uh th No. So let's search for college
Emacs. College flag. No. That's just
something funny about Emacs. Uh but my
uh hosting.
Okay. I think you need to search for um
you need to search on.
Okay. So you need to search in kasali or
which I don't want to do because
kasali.org Or
apart from linguistics and literature
and vocabulary, apart from arts, you
know, arts of human and uh music of
human animals, apart from block uh arts,
all the artworks of humanity.
Uh, some of them are sexual, you know,
for example. That that's that's what you
you zoomers like the the the meme
posters, the [ __ ] posting idiots, young
people, you know, you like this this
type of thing. Oh, this this [ __ ] you
know, [laughter]
I have some of that, you know, for
example, this
uh, you know, and this photo I took
cherry,
you know, like [ __ ]
vagina. Okay. and and and and and it's
quite amazing when you look at flowers,
you know, you have these sexual
illusions.
So they reflect so they actually
reflect, you know, reminds you like what
like what does this ochre reminds you?
It's [ __ ] sex. Okay. Sexual. So so the
sexuality
in plants but also in human animals they
they kind they are kind of connected.
Okay. So you know you see these you know
like [ __ ] exotic extremely alluring
they in they trap men males you know
like you know what what what does this
reminds you of okut you know [laughter]
so so it's it's quite interesting you
know plants um this aspect um I don't
think we can really explain it but it's
part of humanity okay so you got this
plants. You got this beautiful my by the
way this is my favorite flower.
This this is called cyclment. I took
this photo about
uh in uh
when did I took this photo? 200
five. Okay. 20 years ago. Beautiful.
This is kind of my favorite flower.
Okay. [snorts] And they correspond to
you know I associate that you know this
sacrament flower it's amazing because
they flare up you know unlike normal
flower you know normal flowers they open
you know the petals open like that but
this this flower they
they they they start growing downward
then then the the petals like swap up
like women's skirt
Okay. Amazing. You know, I find it just
amazing. And then there's this bazar uh
magazine
has a cover by this girl. This girl is a
supermodel. Used to be known as
supermodel.
Gizo Bunan. By now she's old. You know,
you know the generation come and go. So
women when girls when they are young
they are beautiful. But generations come
and go. They become old. Uh that's
humanity. Okay. And you know we got this
painting from Frederick
Lton
1830s. Okay. Beautiful. Anyway, so
[clears throat]
so I was talking about, you know, all
these uh you know the photos I took. Um
and uh all these are part of
all these are part of kali.org. Okay,
let's go back. Let's go uh back visual
arts and let's go back. In the classic
Greek mythology,
the foundation [snorts]
of the white men of the western society,
you got Europa and the bull. The story
is that the bull which is z
raped, you know, the the white man's
obsessive word rape. The white man is
like
obsessive about this about this concept,
you know. So it didn't happen today. Not
just because social justice war
yesterday it happened 2,000 years ago
3,000 years ago Europa and the bo the z
you know become a bo and grabbed Europa
that's where Europe is named after
became Europe okay Europa and bull
ancient uh you know so this is you know
43 BC and so many so much artworks
Uh and this is quite amazing. And Zoros
gave the girl the girl the zeu which is
the you know one of the most powerful
god
grab the girl and grab the girl and but
he give the girl some gifts. One of them
is this thing
automata. Okay, that's what we are
concerned about. Computing, automation,
robot, Android. This is so this, you
know, if we trace the history, it came
from 2,000 years ago. Automata, okay,
this this Talos, this is this is a bot.
This is a robot who you know goes around
protect
protects Europa the the beautiful girl
you know because the you know this this
is the machine
so the idea came from 2,000 years ago uh
and so we have so many you know so many
so many celebrations and poems and about
the story the
you know Europa and the B so many and
the white And also have these of course
leader and the swang [laughter]
again the zu the all powerful zor
seduced you know the girl you know
grabbed the girl or raped the girl you
know
so anyway that's this these are the
white man's history okay so artwork
amazing
so and of you know you So many. You got
the nymphs. You got the nymphs. Like
today's thoughts on social media over
all over all over all over all over all
over all over all over all over all over
all over all over you. You see these
white girls showing their tits and ass
all over like doing dance or whatever.
[laughter] And today they are now on
chatterbait spreading their legs every
day 24 hours around the clock.
Chatterbait. Okay. the white girls, not
just white girls, but all um races,
okay? Including Chinese and Japanese,
you know, and Korean, they make a lot of
money. Women, that's the nature of
women,
you know, you got nature of men as well.
But anyway,
so you got this, you know, Greek
mythology and you got Medusa, which is
the most ugly girl
in the world. You know, you can't look
at her. The moment you look at her, you
froze because you you don't know what to
do. You know, you [laughter]
that's Medusa. Okay, that's a that's a
classic western
mythology.
Uh,
do you ever find pages on your website
you forgot about? Yeah, of course. That
happens so much. Uh, because by now
after 30 years of blogging, I have about
13,000
uh 13,000 um pages, you know, HTML
and uh every day I, you know, take the
time to maintain them.
So for example I I did this many times.
So you go to the web.
So um you just count the articles then
the
recurs
fi file filter.
Okay. And filter what do you want?
Filter.html.
Okay. Then you pass it to um measure
15,000. So you got 15,000 articles,
okay, on my website, kasadi.info and
kasadi.org. Okay, so constantly I have
articles
I forgot. But I mean, I know, you know,
when I look at them, I remember, you
know, I wrote this, you know, back then,
but you know, but I don't always
remember some articles I've written.
Anyway,
Greek mythology. Okay, very uh deep. So
anyway, I was talking about arts which
is part of Kasadi. Uh so let's go back.
Visual arts kasadi.info. So they are all
part of kasali info, linguistics and
literature and vocabulary,
music and arts and second life. Okay.
But part of it is politics which I did
not link here because I I want to avoid
it. Uh so there are like few hundred
articles about politics about war about
America about
uh you know so I didn't link here you
know but if you really want to read them
you know you can find it.
So anyway what uh what am I doing? So I
was just like random chat and started to
talk about my website
kasali.org. Okay, that's my original.
Then kasali.info is all about
uh mathematics and programming and
technical stuff. So on.info it's less
offensive.
Okay. What am I doing? I don't know. So,
so let's see. Uh, what are you guys
saying? Pull out extra. So, anyway, so I
need another shot. Second shot. Okay,
let's raise a glass class for John
Warak. Okay, let's do because
I don't really know John Warak but um
you know but he's a uh old um
blogger you know before the word I mean
so
mainstream speaking he's a journalist
writing about
uh computing technology the Okay. So,
cheers to John Warak.
So, I remember he wrote article like he
he's the kind of guy. He's kind of
funny. Okay. He always he always make
tonging, you know, make satire kind of
guy and he I remember he used to make
fun of Unix in 1980s. like I came across
his old article like back then you don't
have internet but you have like uh PC
magazine you have like magazines you
know PC magazine and whatever or or Dr.
Dopps you know you guys uh okay so you
guys don't know today but uh for example
Dr. Dobs was a magazine
uh wait Dr. Dob's magazine.
Uh, did I name it correctly? So, you got
uh Dr. Dob's journal. Yeah. So, Dr.
Dobs. So, let's magnify.
Okay. It's a computer journal. Okay. So,
let's go to Wikipedia,
you know. So, you know, back then you
don't have internet. So, you have uh
magazines. Okay.
final issue 2009. So you know internet
killed all these magazines but John
Vorak was used to write for Dr. stops
you know and uh and the PC magazine for
example PC Mac okay that's another
magazine that John Vorak used to write
uh like uh okay cover so you need to say
cover you you can you know like yeah
this is a typical cover of PC magazine
and and there's more there's quite a few
more okay so these magazines today they
or died okay you don't see them anymore.
There's no magazines anymore, but you
can still see them if you go to the
library. Like in USA, you can go to
library and you can borrow. You can
actually see them. So this, you know,
there's PC magazine, there's PC, there's
a Mac magazine. There's so many, you
know, different um Dr. Dob and uh and
John C. Vorac. Let's see. Let's search
for John C. Vorac.
Let's see the Wikipedia. So, John
Civorak. Okay.
So, I How did he die? I suppose died of
old age. Yeah. John Civorak. So, he's
kind of funny and always satirical.
Yeah. So, you know, he his last row was
as a co-host of the No Agenda
podcast. That's the one I mentioned. No.
No agenda podcast is a podcast run by
Adam Curry. Okay. Adam Curry and John
Vorak. They are they are mostly
uh political podcast like they talk
about the you know what's going on in
USA politics. Okay. Mostly
>> [snorts]
>> uh I I kind of watch them for some some
some of them. Uh, it's not really my
thing because I don't I don't like
podcast that much. Uh, so John Adam
Curry, I also don't know this guy, but I
learned Oh, he's only 61. So I learned
he's a he's a he's a
he coined the word podcast. Okay.
Anyway, so that there's that.
John Civorax. So American writer and
broadcaster in the areas of technology
and personal computing. That's right. He
was a column columnist for multiple
magazines since 1980s and wrote or
co-auth or co-authored over a dozen
how-to books on software and technology.
He was vice president on Mayio and was a
host on tech TV and tweet TV. Okay.
Anyway, so yeah.
Okay. So, he passed away. Uh, okay. So,
he's 80 years old. She is
Okay. Yeah. So, he died age 80. So, what
else you guys saying? He raised a glass.
Okay. So, nephew of keyboard inventor.
Oh, you see I didn't know that. I didn't
know they are related. The vorac
keyboard layout.
Uh people are always looking for the B
or N or super perfect Linux. It will
never happen until Microsoft does Linux
draw.
[laughter]
Oh god. Yeah. So that's characteristics
of his
his writing, you know. He's always
making fun of people. He's quite funny
because I I remember like once or twice
I saw him on video or or the podcast the
way he talks, you know, always make fun
of things like always sarcastic.
reminds me of the hot dog guy.
So, we have a guy on SI Discord
and he goes by the handle hot dog. This
guy, he he's always like making fun of
me. All the people like always sarcastic
like he's [laughter]
this guy idiot. Okay, the hot dog guy.
Of course, he's a non, you know, and he
delete
he deletes his post every, you know,
after a week.
Okay, I got a call. Hold on a second. I
got a a call.
Hi guys. Okay, I forgot my microphone is
off. Hi guys, how are you doing? I'm 40%
drunk.
So I'm not wasted. [snorts] Uh I am 30%.
Okay, 30% drunk. So you are watching me.
So you know six years ago when I start
started uh broadcasting live stream on
YouTube I was almost doing it every day
just like today like no goal you know I
just talk random and do it every day.
There's a reason for that. Okay. So but
anyway so so now I started to uh do kind
of just random you know just I just pop
up and talk random. Okay. whatever comes
to mind and looks like people like that.
People are like that. Uh as opposed to
you know in the past two years I try to
be focused. I try to be you know coding
you know coding oriented emac stuff and
stuff that but
half of the time you know it's a bit
complicated but a lot of people you know
that
like like when you talk about technical
or mathematical stuff advanced stuff
people don't understand so they don't
appreciate it on the other hand if you
just talk random like [ __ ] and memes and
you know then you get more viewers you
know people like drama you know that
that's that's a situation
I don't I don't really enjoy this state
of things but that's how things are
anyway so um anyway so whoa the rook is
a car in Chinese chess yes
okay I actually found out about you
through lobbang by the way what do you
think about uh IKU. Okay. Uh that's
quite interesting. You found about me
via my lobbang tutorial. That's quite
interesting because
because uh because my lobbang is kind of
old, you know, 20 years ago and I
haven't done with anything with it and
you know so I can tell you a story
because I realized
you know back then 20 years ago or 30
years ago I was a fan of Logebang. So,
so let me talk about Lojang. Are you
still here? You know, I know I know I
haven't been answering like your comment
is is like 30 minutes ago. [laughter]
Okay. So, let me tell you about
Logebang. Okay.
Uh L O J BN. So, I don't have a
bookmark. So, let's go to kasali.info.
Let's go to kasali.org.
showing browser and let's go to uh
logebang. So you need to go to uh wordy
English
um
do I logebang okay so logebang is a
so-called artificial language
or today they call it constructed
language
so it's a it's a language for human like
English, French, Spanish, Russian,
Chinese and so on. But it's constructed.
That means it's artificially created.
Why is that? Because in natural
languages like English, Spanish, Russian
and and so on, the grammar is very
complex. The vocabulary is very complex
and irregular, you know, so it's very
difficult to learn. Of course, usually
you grew up with it, so you don't have a
problem. But from a logical point of
view, it's like so complex, you know. So
people started to create artificial
languages
or called constructed languages starting
about uh I think starting about 1800s.
The most famous is Espirando. Okay,
Espirando.
You can see Espirando. Okay, it's a most
famous uh constructed language. Let me
read it. Okay. Espirono
is the world's most widely spoken
constructed auxiliary language. Meaning
it's not a natural language. It's a
language people created like people
designed like like a programming
language. Okay. [snorts]
Uh created by LL Zamhof in 1887 as the
international language. Okay. So why
they do that? Basically they do that
because to learn a natural language
let's say you know you are an English
speaker and you are trying to learn
French or Russian or Chinese typically
you find it extremely complex you know
like the grammar is like convoluted the
vocabulary is so many irregularities you
know
why does that happen that well that's
that happens because that's the way
natural languages evolve S it's not like
God designed it you know 200 2,000 years
ago like God thought about everything
you know design just you know came out
with one English that's not the case
English came from
English is a plebbeian language um which
came from kind of German like little
tribes okay that's a history of English
anyway then but then then English got so
much influence from from French and
Spanish is so so it's like a bag of
garbage you know it's like so many
irregularities
but usually you wouldn't know if you are
native English speakers because you grew
up with it until but when when you start
to learn French or or Spanish then you
you realized oh my god this language is
so complicated then you start to think
well that's actually that's a case you
know for example for for French people
or Chinese people or Russian when they
learn English they they got all this
like complex [ __ ] like [ __ ] up
basically it's a pure baggage
okay that's a situation that's natural
languages okay
so people around 1800 they started to
create constructed languages like
Espirando is the most famous. So they
designed the language from the ground
up. So it's all regular, you know, they
they they think about, okay, so we we
have we need nouns, we need verbs, you
know, they create vocabulary for them.
You need um you know, articles, you
know, whatever grammatical words and or
the of, you know, things like that. So
they they create the language. So it's
all regular and and
easy to learn. Okay, that's the
that's the momentum that's that's why
this constructed language will created.
Okay, just
[sighs] uh I don't know where I'm going
so I'm just talking random. I don't know
how many people are watching. Five. Uh I
hope you guys like it and if you are
still here say something. Okay.
So they created
artificial languages. Okay.
And what is the purpose? You know back
then people were thinking you know if we
can create a easy tole learn artificial
language then everyone can learn it. So
it can became a international language
like universal language. So instead of
learning French to talk to French
people, you have to learn Russian to
talk to Russian people. You know, you
have to learn so many uh Japan uh
Japanese or Chinese or or Spanish or
African.
You can just learn this one language.
Everyone can learn this easy easy to
learn because it's so regular. So
everyone can communicate. So it, you
know, it's like a utopia vision.
Okay, it's a utopian vision. That's what
these people were thinking.
[laughter]
Actually, logically, it makes sense, but
in reality,
it didn't work. Okay, it didn't work.
Um,
there's there's a lot of reasons. Okay.
So we we we we we we can dive into the
history of constructed language and and
how they became. So but in reality it
doesn't work out. It doesn't really work
out that way.
So anyway, so anyway, so today we got
AI. So AI can translate languages on the
fly. So that kind of became like the
solution for international
communication. Today AI is so amazing.
You know, you can talk to AI. You can
talk to AI in in Chinese, in Japanese,
in English, in French, in in Mexican, in
Russian. Like you can mix it and AI
understand it. I because I I've done so.
Let me let me show you. Okay. So,
so let me let me talk about in Chinese.
Okay. Chinese and English mixed. So, you
can see AI because I know Chinese. Okay.
So AI today understand all these
languages and you can mix them and it it
can translate on the fly. It's just like
amazing. Okay.
Okay. Speak that in. English.
>> Yeah, I agree. A lot of AI models now
handle dozens of languages. Translation,
conversation, writing, you name it.
>> Can you say that in Japanese?
Say that in Russian.
I want to find a white girlfriend. I
think the Russians are the most
beautiful. How can I do that? Can you
Can you explain in Chinese?
can you say that in English?
>> If you want a white girlfriend and think
Russians are the most beautiful, I can
help brainstorm ways to meet them.
Meeting someone from another country
takes time and real effort. Apps,
travel, or language exchange are the
main paths.
>> Okay, say that in Spanish.
Can you say that in Arabics?
Now try that in person.
Now, can you do that in Espiranto?
quite amazing. What the [ __ ] AI, you
know? It's it it speaks in Persian, in
Espiranto,
in Arabics,
in Spanish, in Russian, in Chinese, it
all in Japanese. understand everything.
Amazing AI. So AI is like robbed my job,
you know. AI is robbing my
intellectualism.
Anyway, so yeah. So there it is. So So
um
yeah, so I was talking about Espiranto,
the artificial constructed language. Now
let me introduce you guys about Ljwang.
So loshbang is another constructed
language but this time there's something
different because loshbang is based on
predicate logic you know like one of the
field of mathematics because the people
believe that
you know the human languages
you know there's a lot grammatical
irregularities
vocabulary irregularities
but what about like The Luan people they
address the logic.
Can you have like actually pure
mathematical logic system as a as a
natural human language?
That is when
log land it was born. Okay. So lobbang.
So let me tell you guys the history of
Lobbang. Okay. So can we um actually let
me show you guys the Wikipedia article
because then it'll be more clear. Okay.
So Lj Brown originally was the log land
logical language.
Okay. So here here is the article. So
log land is a constructed
human language based on predicate logic.
Okay. Llan. So let me read it. Logan is
a logical constructed language
originally designed for linguistic
research
particularly for investigating the Seper
Wolf hypothesis.
The language was developed beginning in
1955 by Dr. James Cook Brown with the
goal of making the language so so
different from natural languages that
people learning it would think in a
different way
if the hypothesis were true. Okay. So
what is the sapper wolf hypothesis?
Separ hypothesis basically says that
the language you speak influence your
thought you know so most of you speak
English so it actually influence your
perception about the world uh uh about
the you know your logic deduction
whatever
so if you actually speak French or
another language
you will actually have a different view
of the world.
Uh you know so that's kind of the uh
sapper wolf hypothesis. So let me read
it. Let me read it. So uh I guess these
days they call it linguistic relativity.
Uh that's new to me. Okay. So linguistic
relativity asserts that language
influences world view or cognition.
One form of linguistic relativity,
linguistic determinism, regards people's
languages as a determining and
influencing the scope of cultural
perceptions of their surrounding world.
So anyway, the the short version, the
sapper wolf hypothesis
means that
languages determines your thought. Okay?
Determines your world view.
So if you are English, if you are a
native English speaker, the way you view
the word is would be different from a
French speaker or Russian speaker or
Chinese speaker. Okay, that's what
sapper wolf hypothesis means. You know
it's not about
you know fairness or you know what is
truth or because what is true depends on
what language you speak that's the
essence of the sapper wolf hypothesis
you know if you speak l English if you
speak English is your native language
then then you are sure to be to be
biased in some way if you speak you
natively uh Russian you are sure to be
biased in some other way that's what
this means okay sapper wolf hypothesis
so the the the lock article language was
spawn they they want to create a
language constructed language purely
based on logic so that it removes all
these restrictions
of these uh bias you and perceptions.
The idea is that if you can base a
natural human language on logic, then
you would have a kind of extremely
powerful perception because now your
language is free of all the restrictions
and cultural biases of the sapper wolf,
you know, issue.
Okay, that that is origin. That's that's
the that's why log land was born. Okay.
Now what about Logebang? You know, so
what you know, basically Logebang
happened because the Land people, the
James Cook Brown copyright the Lland.
[laughter] So you know it's like the
open source, you know, they copyright.
So you can you cannot learn it with, you
know, you you have to like pay or
whatever. It's proprietary.
Then people, you know, the the log land
community, they don't like it. So they
created their own lobban language
basically the same idea uh you know the
same idea as a log line but the the
human you know basically it's a
power struggle you know this guy created
log land I was learning it but he says
you have to pay because it's proprietary
copyright so some people didn't like it
so they created their own lolland
lobbang that's why Lobang was created.
So there's a legal like they they try to
um
sue you know they they they um like
origin from Lland you can read the
history you see they they tried to
lawsuit each other so that is that is
why lobbang
was created. Okay. And this is kind of
this lobbang is what I learned.
Power struggle power struggle among
human animals because you believe that's
you know that's yours and I believe I
want something else
[sighs]
for the you know for the for money
basically ultimately for money.
So anyway that's that's the origin of
lobbang. Okay. So, uh, okay. I don't
know what I'm going where I'm going. So,
maybe that's it for today. Um,
do you know the odd joke about
Espiranto?
It's the only language everyone speaks
with an accent. I've heard that it never
really took off because of the WW1 and2
even though it's it had a lot of
potential. No, I didn't know about that.
I don't know what that means.
But anyway, I know that Espiranto is
very popular in China. In fact, I know
that Espiranto is like China was the
most promoter of Espiranto.
Now you have to you know the reason for
that is back in 1950s
you know China
ch you know China the communist China
they were trying to uh
they were trying to
refresh Chinese because Chinese is very
difficult to learn because you got all
these thousand 3,000 characters takes
years like six five years to But so they
wanted to simplify you know so they
created simplified characters but
basically they you know among the
Chinese intellectuals
around 1950s or around even the
beginning of 1900s they wanted to create
you know they wanted to
advance chi China so they they you know
so they think that Chinese is a problem
because it just you know too many too
complex to learn so they want to
modernize Chinese
so they created simplified characters
but that's not enough so one of the
thought you know one of the branch of
the intellectuals is that you know maybe
maybe we can you know try espironto you
know we can you know maybe we can use
espironto which is very simple
artificial you know artificial
not you know human language based on
alphabets so you don't have like
complicated Chinese writings okay
uh do you guys know what I mean I you
know I can like show you um
you know I can show you like Chinese
writings
I've done that before
uh so you need to um
so you need to open this with uh open
with uh info view and pen. Okay, let's
open with pen. Okay, so you can see I'm
writing Chinese.
Okay, this is Chinese.
Uh I don't remember my Chinese.
uh so how do I write complex
I don't remember [laughter] that's one
the problem of Chinese because every
character is a word and you have to
remember you have to memorize how to
write it if you don't do it every day
you forgot so right now I want to write
how you know I want to write complex
complexity
but I forgot how to write said I don't
remember.
So this is Chinese. So the people are
thinking you know the Chinese
intellectuals they are thinking we got
to do something about it because Chinese
is you know an obstacle to learning to
modernization to nuclear bombs you know.
So we have to do something about this
Chinese education like like remove
Chinese language you know adopt the
alphabet system something like that. So
that's that was the thought. So China
actually promoted espironto a lot
because I remember
for example on Wikipedia if you search
China
I think you'll find it. you see by
country
uh they'll talk about it you know so
China actually promoted a lot espironto
you know there's a lot like there's a
radio in China talking in espironto and
stuff okay
uh Chinese okay so can we find Chinese
um media the Chinese government has used
esbrronto since 2011 I mean since 200
2001 for an espironto version of its
China internet information center. China
also uses espironto in China radio
international and for the internet
magazine El
Propola
Chino. Okay. So you can see you see ch
China was promoting espironto for a
while
because China you know Chinese were
thinking they need to replace Chinese to
um to move forward to modernize.
Anyway, so Esronto. Okay, so you got
Esronto, you got Lojivan, then you got
you got quite a few other constructed
languages and one of them is the the one
you mentioned. Um there's quite a few.
Okay. So I mean if you look at the
constructed languages then you can see
quite a few.
So you can see they even have a kind of
a logo. So you got um history, you got
constructed languages, you got
uh history, you got you know so um
so basically there's quite a few by now.
Okay. So but but there's one thing they
share in common is that they they all
have a kind of a utopian
vision.
So at you know at one point they think
it should be the international language
auxiliary language okay 19th and 20th
century.
So you can see Espironto mentioned
uh in Encyclopedia
and stuff and Volapo is one of the early
ones Espironto there
and also it turns out they disagree. You
see for example I invented espironto
then after a while some people you know
they are also learning espironto they
share the vision but after a while they
disagree you know another guy a [ __ ]
usually so they they think no no I
disagree with your view so they splinter
and branched off with another new
language like inter lingua so
interlingua is another constructive
language you know because we disagree.
So you can see there is power struggle
issue among males. Okay, power struggle
essentially that's what's going on. So
you know what why should we you know if
you we you know if we all going to adopt
esto then the human history is going to
just remember you you know the the zam
or whatever that guy you know oh you you
were the guy who created it.
No no no I I'm I'm going to create my my
a name for myself. I'm going to create a
new branch of Espironto. I'm gonna, you
know, this fix some of the problems you
have so the history will remember me. So
I'm gonna, you know, start to make
money. I'm gonna become a hero. That's
that's that's a lot of the reason for
the split. Okay? You know, so
so they disagree. So you know, so you
got, you know, so you got several
others.
Okay? So anyway, that's kind of the um
a short take my my kind of short take of
the constructed languages. Okay. And
then then you can so if you are a
academics
you can categorize the different
constructed languages. For example, you
can categorize by how they are
engineered or you can categorize by
their purpose or you can categorize by
their artistic language. For example,
artistic for example artistic what what
what are some examples? You know the
Star Trek the Star Trek created the
you know that race
uh Klingong you know [laughter]
the Star Trek created created Klingong
you know there there it is Star Trek. So
you can you can classify all the the
lord of the rings created you know their
own language you know so you can
classify by artistic uh merit
and then you know several others so
anyway
so on the whole so there's clingong on
the whole I so back in 30 years ago I
was a big fan of lobbang
because I think it's a logical language
based on you know the logic predicate
logic mathematics so that I thought that
this will revolution you know this will
make you see
things that you it's not possible with
English or Chinese because this language
is purely logical based on mathematics
that was my thought
but over the years I thought you know I
started to think no that's not really
the case because
um
because human languages and human
thought is fairly complicated
you know like nobody really know
exactly how it works okay like nobody
you know nobody really know how it works
Um
so the the the lobbang or llan
constructed language artificial language
based on logic
that's interesting okay that's
interesting but
but I wouldn't say that is the final
like the absolute final you know
uh idea uh nobody because because we
don't really understand the whole thing
Because for example today AI there's a
question what does intelligence means?
You know is AI intelligent?
We don't know you know after 40 years
after 50 years after six years of
artificial intelligence history
today we have the AI bots but we still
don't know what what exactly what what
does intelligent means. Now AI can write
poems and although you know can can play
chess can write poems but but we know
it's like it's it's you know it's not a
real human is it doesn't really feel
anything.
So what does it mean when actually feel
something we don't know. So that's you
know we still don't know actually we are
learning a lot. So that so anyway that's
my commentary.
Okay,
that's it for today, I think.
Or should I stay and uh uh do whatever?
No one's going to be the linguistics
Jesus.
So, can you write in ping?
Uh can I write in ping? Yeah, of course.
Uh ping. Yeah. So, okay. So in order to
write pins so let's start notebook
and uh okay notebook Microsoft notebook
okay why is that uh why do I get why is
it not responding I don't know
uh wait go back uh go back what
so you go back to notebook book
uh there. Okay.
Oh yeah, because it was in uh opening
some stupid file. Okay, so wait, what?
Okay, so new notebook. Okay, something.
Okay, now magnify. Now, uh can I write
in pin? Yes, I learned that about 20
years ago. So, window space to switch to
ping in input there. Okay, now let's
write Chinese.
Okay, that wait what?
Yeah, you need to press space. Okay,
that this means Chinese. Okay. Uh let's
say I love you. Okay. So
that means I love you. Now press space.
See that's I love you.
Okay that's ping. So uh but it takes a
lot practice. So I haven't practiced. So
if I were to talk to a Chinese person it
will take me a lot of time because
a lot of time you need to learn. I mean,
you need to like um
like if if I were to write an article in
Chinese, it'll take like an hour because
then I need to think about what what's
the right character, you know? I forgot.
So, anyway, that's ping. Uh okay, I
think that's it for today.
It feels kind of in to drop Chinese. how
much content and culture there is in it
and switch to espironto.
Yeah, that's another issue about these
constructed languages because if you
drop uh English, you know, if you drop
English for example, that's a issue in
India.
India for some for for reasons they
adopted English as their kind of their
for their educated class in India.
That's why on Twitter you see a lot
Indians like spam
scam in English and they are from India
but they but English is kind of their
native language even though the the way
they speak it is you know usually is
offensive to the white men because they
they speaking Indian accent. Actually, I
have a video. I have a fun video. Uh,
let's see if I can find it.
Indian English. Okay. So, let me switch
to
uh US. Okay. Uh,
okay. I find it
Indian English. Okay. Like there's a
video very funny the way Indian I mean
that the video is trying to make fun of
Indian. Okay. So
um
wait is is there a special word for uh I
don't think I can find it. So that's an
Indian mathematician
uh Indian scum posting fake news.
There's a lot of it you know lots of
these scam came from in you know from
India
they they post like they just post drama
and fake news like you know and you
don't know who they are until until this
year Peter started to show their
location.
So a lot of these Indians they pretend
to be white men like they are pro-
western culture. They are like the
Greeks or whatever you know the the the
the Christians or you know pro-Christian
whatever
crap Indian. So anyway so India speaks
um you know so that's an Indian uh
popular game.
>> This game is called
Uh
so there is a funny uh video that makes
for example this guy inevitable west
it's a Indian scum a scammer okay you
know like according to his profile it
says defender of western values and
culture Jesus Christ is king account run
from England
But if you but but since like two a year
ago they started to show origin. Okay.
Oh account based in United Kingdom.
But anyway this account used well known
to it's it's from it's a India. It's a
Indian. Okay.
Now uh how do I prove it? I don't know
how to prove it but I don't I stopped
following mean is there this millions of
drama so if you try to trace you can
never find it but this this one
uh
this one is a well known you know it's a
Indian scammer but I can't you know I
can't prove it to you now
but anyway so Indian so there is a um is
there a kind of a fun video
about English. Very funny. Okay. Uh, and
this Nikki Harley is a war monger. Is a
[ __ ] scum. It's a truly scum. Okay.
This Nikki Harley, I didn't know 10
years ago. But you see, the the things
you learn about politics usually takes
you over 10 years to realize what's
really going on.
Anyway, there there's a funny Indian uh
English uh
video. Uh
I think I repost it, but I can't find
it. Okay, that's another problem with
Twitter.
Okay,
I think that's it for today.
Thank you guys for watching.
Three concurrent viewers. How long have
I been going? I've been going on for 1
hour and 40 minutes. 100 minutes.
Okay. Bye, guys.